# **CARLOS CORREDOR**

# **FULL STACK DEVELOPER GEOPHYSICAL ENGINEERING ELECTRONIC**

After 30 years teaching mathematics, physics, electrical networks and geophysical instrumentation, I am now dedicated to the exciting world of programming as a web developer in the following technologies: Javascript, React, Redux, Sass, Less, Node, Express, MongoDB, Mongoose, PostgreSQL, Sequelize.

#### CONTAC ME



@carloscorredorwg



carloscorredorwg@gmail.com



Carlos7979



carloscorredorwg



+1 (262) 309-8763

# **LENGUAGES**

Spanish: Bilingual or native proficiency

English: B1 Intermediate (listening) C2 Proeficient (reading)

### WORK EXPERIENCE

Full stack programmer

Owly (2023) - LQQH (2023 - 2024)

Contributions:

Full stack programmer in remote mode

# Full Stack Teaching Assistant

Henry - Bootcamp

August 2021- September 2021

Contributions:

- Guide students in their first steps
- Personalized attention for code review
- Follow-up of the individual process of the students
- Contribution of ideas to improve Bootcamp processes

#### Founding Partner, Project Manager

Alterna MDC

February 2017 – present

Contributions:

- Management of the flow of electronic modules and inventory through functional programming implemented through spreadsheets.
- Management of the company website.

# Instructor Professor

Universidad Central de Venezuela

Faculty of Engineering

Department of Applied Mathematics

October 2013 - March 2019

- Full-time instructor teacher: • Linear Algebra Chair Coordinator.
- Calculus II Chair Coordinator.
- Teaching Calculus I, Calculus II, Calculus III and Linear Algebra.

#### **TECH SKILLS**

#### **CLIENT SIDE:**

- Html
- Css
- JavaScript
- Sass
- Less
- **i**Ouery
- TDD (Vanilla JS and Jasmine)
- External API's
- React JS
- Vue
- Redux

















#### **SERVER SIDE**







- NodeJS
- ExpressJS
- Server-side rendering with PUG and Handlebars
- MongoDB
- PostgreSQL
- TDD (Mocha, Chai, NYC & Istanbul)



#### **TEAM WORKING:**

- Scrum
- Agile
- Git
- Trello



#### **OTHERS**

Octave



#### **PROYECTS**

- Vue Bakery
- Food calendar
- Dogs
- · Flow control of electronic control modules
- E-commerce Nozama
- Check list

# **TRAINING**

Vue Is

Coder House (2023)



Testing QA Manual Coder House (2023)

Full-Stack Web Development Henry - Bootcamp (2021)

Machine Learning Coursera (2021)

Full-Stack Web Development

ISDI Coders - Bootcamp (2019)













Industrial Bachelor Electronic Mention U.E. Thomas Alva Edison (1997)

